<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on JRHacka</title>
    <link>https://jrhacka.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on JRHacka</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2022, Jake Rice and the Hugo Authors; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jrhacka.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Like John Hammond from Jurassic World, but Cooler</title>
      <link>https://jrhacka.github.io/post/johnhammondvideo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jrhacka.github.io/post/johnhammondvideo/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            &lt;p&gt;What an incredible honor and experience it was to hang out with John for a little bit! We had a blast talking about the industry, some advice for people new to the industry, and then what it&#39;s like creating content and going to work at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hozah for Wazuh</title>
      <link>https://jrhacka.github.io/post/wazuh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jrhacka.github.io/post/wazuh/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            &lt;p&gt;Everyone welcome to my Ted Talk. This post is primarily going to be a discussion on SIEM’s in general, and then on what my initial thoughts were on Wazuh. The installation instructions online are excellent, so I’m going to let you all use that instead of me just rewriting them. Please refer to the video if you do get stuck or have questions!&lt;/p&gt;
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who&#39;s That Netmon?!?!</title>
      <link>https://jrhacka.github.io/post/netmon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jrhacka.github.io/post/netmon/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            &lt;p&gt;Yes that title was a Pokemon reference, and if you didn&#39;t understand it I feel sorry for you. This is my walkthrough of the HTB Netmon box. Enjoy, and find my walkthough below!&lt;/p&gt;
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CoCanDa Forever</title>
      <link>https://jrhacka.github.io/post/cocanda/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jrhacka.github.io/post/cocanda/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            &lt;p&gt;It was just a matter of time before a marvel reference came in to play... Follow along with me as we dive into a challenge from Blue Team Labs Online. New website and new fun content as we break apart an email from an alien hostage taker!&lt;/p&gt;
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing the Malware... Kinda</title>
      <link>https://jrhacka.github.io/post/malwareanalysispt1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jrhacka.github.io/post/malwareanalysispt1/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            &lt;p&gt;In the spirit of getting better everyday I downloaded some malicious files from the site &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.virusshare.com&#34;&gt;www.virusshare.com&lt;/a&gt; and am going to be spending some time playing around with them. I&#39;ll be using my REMNux VM and seeing what all I can figure out. Follow along for some beginner moves and learn with me along the way! Find the walkthrough video below and enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>REMnux &gt; Numchucks</title>
      <link>https://jrhacka.github.io/post/remnux_setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jrhacka.github.io/post/remnux_setup/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            &lt;p&gt;This title was certainly reaching a bit, but it&#39;ll do. REMnux is an incredible versatile and useful malware analysis machine. This post is meant to not only educate you about it, but walk you through its setup!&lt;/p&gt;
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 7 Hours of Creation</title>
      <link>https://jrhacka.github.io/post/bundle/hugopost/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jrhacka.github.io/post/bundle/hugopost/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Yes this title is a play on words, and yes you are going to see a lot more of them. It didn’t actually take 7 hours, but this is the process and steps I used for creating my website.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lame is Cool</title>
      <link>https://jrhacka.github.io/post/lame/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jrhacka.github.io/post/lame/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            &lt;p&gt;Clever titles for days. This walkthough of the Lame box is another begginner friendly entry level HTB. We&#39;ll explore a little anonymous FTP, and find out more about Samba. You can find the walkthrough video down below!&lt;/p&gt;
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This is my Legacy</title>
      <link>https://jrhacka.github.io/post/legacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jrhacka.github.io/post/legacy/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            &lt;p&gt;The clever titles just don&#39;t stop! This is my walkthrough of the Legacy HTB. Enjoy, find the video below, and reach out if you have any questions.&lt;/p&gt;
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
